HEADS AGAIN. THAT'S 18.
19.
AND...
[chuckles]
VOILAÀ.
I BELIEVE
THAT'S THE WAGER.
PAY UP.
OKAY. SO WHAT'S THE TRICK?TRICK?
TELL ME WHAT THE TRICK IS,
AND I WILL GIVE YOU THE MONEY.
THE TRICK IS...
[whispers]
I HAVE SUPERNATURAL POWERS.
IT'S A 2-HEADED COIN,
RIGHT?
LOOKS NORMAL TO ME.
HMM.
YOU DID SOMETHING TO THE COIN,
RIGHT?
COME ON, MAN.
I GAVE YOU 20 BUCKS.
[chuckles]
UH, CAN I HELP YOU?AM I IN THE WAY?
KIMBALL SAID
I COULD SIT HERE.KIMBALL?
I'M A FRIEND OF HIS.
ELISE CHAY.
ELISE, YES.
YEAH, I'M THERESA LISBON.
CHO'S TALKED ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU MUST BE RIGSBY.
OH, HEY. WAYNE.
IT'S A PLEASURE.
IT IS. I LIKE PUTTING FACES
TO NAMES.
UM, I HAVE TO ASK YOU--
PATRICK JANE--IS--OVER HERE.
OH. HI.HI.
[lowered voice] I THOUGHT
HE'D LOOK SCARIER.
[lowered voice]
HE'S RESTING.
HEY.HEY.
I WAS JUST MEETING EVERYBODY.
YEAH, WE WERE JUST GETTING
TO THE EMBARRASSING QUESTIONS.
AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE LEAVING.
OUR RESERVATION'S AT 8:00.
WELL, IT WAS NICE
MEETING YOU ALL.HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
[telephone rings]LET ME JUST GET THIS.
OKAY,
I'LL BE BY THE ELEVATOR.ALL RIGHT.
CHO.Uh, Agent Kimball Cho?
THAT'S RIGHT.IT'S DETECTIVE SHARON FLOREY,
OAKLAND HOMICIDE.
I JUST CAUGHT A SHOOTING
ON THE EAST SIDEI'M HOPING
YOU CAN HELP ME OUT WITH IT.UH, IF YOU WANT
CBI's ASSISTANCE, DETECTIVE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO RUN IT
BY THE SPECIAL AGENT IN CHARGE.
NO, I'M--I'M NOT ASKING
FOR CBI, AGENT, JUST YOU.ME? WHY?
Well, we haven't I.D.'d
the victim yet,
BUT WE GOT HIS PHONE.
THERE WERE THREE CALLS TO YOUR
NUMBER IN THE PAST FEW DAYS.
That bring a name to mind?
WHAT'S THE VICTIM LOOK LIKE?
ASIAN MALE, EARLY 30s,
prison tats.
Uh, gangbanger, probably.
WHAT'S THE ADDRESS?[thud]
3700 Heller Way, Oakland.
[clicks pen]
ALL RIGHT.
I'M ON MY WAY.Thanks.
DUTY CALLS?
IT'S A HOMICIDE IN OAKLAND.
THEY WANT HELP WITH THE I.D.
YOU'RE GONNA DISAPPOINT
THAT LOVELY YOUNG LADY
WAITING OUT BY THE ELEVATOR
FOR A CORPSE? IN OAKLAND?
A JOB'S A JOB.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
NO. I'LL DO THIS ALONE.
[thunder crashes]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
AGENT CHO.
DETECTIVE FLOREY.
VICTIM TOOK
THREE BULLETS IN THE BACK.
WALLET'S MISSING, BUT I DON'T
THINK IT WAS A ROBBERY.
HE STILL HAD HIS PHONE
ON HIM
AND SOME CASH
IN HIS BACK POCKET,
ALSO THIS--
MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
NO.
HIS NAME'S DAVID SEUNG,
GOT OUT SIX MONTHS AGO
AFTER DOING TIME AT FOLSOM.
HE'S A BANGER,
MEMBER
OF THE AVON PARK PLAYBOYS.
AVON PARK PLAYBOYS?
MY OLD GANG.YOU RAN WITH THE PLAYBOYS?
SEUNG'S ONLY FAMILY IS
HIS GRANDMOTHER, SAME LAST NAME.
SHE LIVES ON TELEGRAPH AVENUE.KNOW WHAT HE'D BEEN UP TO
SINCE GETTING OUT?
NO IDEA. HAVEN'T TALKED TO HIM
IN 13 YEARS.WHAT ABOUT THOSE CALLS?
HE LEFT A COUPLE MESSAGES,
SAID HE NEEDED HELP.
YOU DIDN'T CALL HIM BACK
AND FIND OUT WHY?
NO.
ANYTHING ELSE, DETECTIVE?
WE'RE GOOD.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.THANK YOU.
[horn honks in distance]
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S THE STORY?
YOU HEARD THE STORY.
WHY DID HE CALL YOU FOR HELP?
ARE YOU FRIENDS?
WE USED TO BE BEST FRIENDS.
HE WAS LIKE MY BROTHER.
Captioning made possible
by T-Mobile. Stick Together.
Captioned by
Closed Captioning Services, Inc.
MORNING.
DOES THAT LOOK FUNNY TO YOU?
LIKE, THICKER?
WHY?
I'M THINKING JANE
WEIGHTED IT ON ONE SIDE
SO THAT
IT ALWAYS LANDS HEADS.
EXCEPT WHEN I FLIP IT,
IT DOESN'T ALWAYS
LAND HEADS.
IT COMES UP TAILS
HALF THE TIME.
MAYBE THERE'S
A TECHNIQUE OF TOSSING IT.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING ENOUGH SEX
FROM VAN PELT.
HEY. SHH.
WE DON'T TALK ABOUT THAT.[woman] KIMBALL.
MRS. SEUNG.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
YOU NEVER VISITED HIM
IN PRISON, DID YOU?
NO.
12 YEARS IS A LONG TIME.
I TOLD DAVID ABOUT YOU,
WHEN YOU JOINED THE ARMY,
WHEN YOU BECAME
A POLICE OFFICER.
HE ALWAYS LOOKED UP TO YOU.
YOU'LL BE WORKING TO FIND
WHO KILLED HIM, WON'T YOU?
NO, MA'AM. THE CASE BELONGS
TO THE OAKLAND POLICE.
THEY'LL FIND
WHOEVER DID THIS.
THAT DETECTIVE WOMAN--
SHE THINKS DAVID GOT KILLED
BECAUSE HE WAS IN THE GANG.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.IT DOES LOOK LIKE
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
NO. HE LEFT THE GANG.
HE HAD A JOB.
JUST BECAUSE HE TOLD YOU HE LEFT
THE GANG DOESN'T MEAN HE DID.HE WOULDN'T LIE TO ME.
MRS. SEUNG,
WHEN I KNEW DAVID,
I HEARD HIM LIE TO YOU
MANY TIMES,
ABOUT WHAT HE WAS DOING,
WHO HE WAS WITH.
THE OAKLAND POLICE
WILL HANDLE IT, OKAY?
PLEASE, KIMBALL.
WON'T YOU HELP?
I'M SORRY, MRS. SEUNG.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
SO HE WAS A FRIEND OF YOURS?
IT WAS
A GUY I USED TO KNOW.
LOOK, WE'LL COVER FOR YOU
IF YOU WANT TO TAKE COMP TIME
TO LOOK INTO IT.ABSOLUTELY.
BOSS WON'T MIND.
I'M NOT GETTING INVOLVED.
BUT HE WAS YOUR FRIEND.
HE WAS A GANGBANGER, VAN PELT.
BANGERS GET SHOT.
ALL RIGHT, HE'S NOT THE FIRST
GUY I USED TO KNOW TO GET SHOT.
HE WON'T BE THE LAST.THAT'S FUNNY.
GRANDMA OUT THERE
SEEMED PRETTY CERTAIN
HE WAS NO LONGER A GANG MEMBER.SHE'S WRONG.
SHE SEEMED PRETTY SHARP.MAYBE HE GOT SHOT 'CAUSE HE WAS
TRYING TO LEAVE THE GANG.
THAT HAPPENS, DOESN'T IT?
WHATEVER. OAKLAND'S GOT IT.
HOW MUCH TIME IS OAKLAND P.D.
GONNA SPEND ON A GANGBANGER?
NOT MUCH.
WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
WELL, THERE MUST BE
SOMEONE THAT CAN TELL US
THAT HE WAS OR WASN'T
A MEMBER OF THE GANG.
I MEAN, JUST FOR KICKS.NO.
OKAY, THEN, UH,
JUST TO...
SOOTHE
YOUR TROUBLED CONSCIENCE.
[horns honking in distance]
SO THE MEAN STREETS, HUH?YEP.
YOUR OLD STOMPING GROUND.
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
STOLE A CAR OVER THERE
WHEN I WAS 14.
YEAH?
CRASHED IT OVER THERE.
MM.
DON'T WANDER.NO WORRIES.
[scoffs] WE'RE CLOSED.
JON JON.
CHO.
IS THAT YOU FOR REAL?
YEAH.
MAN, I HEARD YOU WAS A COP.
I SAID, NO WAY.
DAWG, THIS IS KIMBALL CHO.
YEAH, I SEE HIM.
HE'S A PLAYBOY
FROM WAY BACK.
CALLED HIM THE "ICE MAN."
NO.
YEAH, YOU WANTED SOMETHING
DONE COLD, YOU GOT CHO.
WELL, IT'S STILL THE SAME.WHO ARE YOU?
UH. PATRICK JANE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
GREAT STORE.
UH, SOME KIND OF DRUG DEALERSHIP
IS IT, YEAH?
NAH.
YOU KNOW,
I READ SOMEWHERE THAT--
AND THIS IS VERY INTERESTING--
THE AVERAGE DRUG DEALER
WOULD MAKE A BETTER WAGE
SERVING BURGERS.
IS THAT ACCURATE,
DO YOU THINK?
[chuckles] THERE'S CHUMPS
AND THERE'S PLAYERS
IN ANY GAME, BRO.
I GUESS.
HEY.
YOU HEAR ABOUT DAVID SEUNG?
OH. YEAH.
ANY IDEA WHO KILLED HIM?NO.
WAS HE ROLLING
WITH YOU GUYS AGAIN?
IS THAT WHAT GOT HIM
IN TROUBLE?WHY WOULD I TELL YOU ANYTHING?
I JUST WANT TO CONFIRM
IT'S A GANG BEAND I'LL LEAVE IT ALONE.WHEN DAVID GOT OUT OF PRISON, WE
ASKED HIM TO PUT IN SOME WORK,
GET HIM BACK IN THE GROOVE,
YOU KNOW? HE SAID NO.
HE WAS QUITTING. HE QUIT.
THEN ABOUT A MONTH AGO,
HE CALLS AND HE'S ALL,
"I NEED TO TALK TO K.S.
DIRECT,"
LIKE HE HAD
SOME KIND OF DEAL.
SO HE'S WORKING WITH K.S.
AND NOT THE GANG?
THAT'S WRONG.
THAT'S DISRESPECT.
YOU'RE IN OR YOU'RE OUT.
AIN'T NO HALFWAY.
RIGHT, ICE MAN?
WHAT KIND OF DEAL?
DON'T KNOW.
I DO KNOW K.S. IS SERIOUSLY MAD
AT YOU FOR WHAT YOU DID.
WELL,
HE SHOULD LEARN TO LET GO.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
OH, JON JON, UM, THESE NUMBERS
MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
[sniffs] NO.
YOU CERTAIN?
YEAH.
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN?
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING.
YOU KNOW,
YOUR OBSESSION WITH EATING
IS AN INFANTILE ATTEMPT
OF COPING WITH THE PERSISTENT
ANXIETY YOU FEEL.
NOW IF I MAY RECOMMEND
SOMETHING?
A CAREER CHANGE.
IT'LL BE VERY GOOD FOR YOU.
DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT, UH, WHO CAME UP
WITH "AVON PARK PLAYBOYS"?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT VERY TOUGH.YEAH, THAT'S FUNNY.
LET'S GO BACK TO SACRAMENTO.
ICE MAN--UM, I KNOW WHERE
IT COMES FROM, BUT I JUST...
[cell phone rings]JUST TELL ME YOU DIDN'T COME UP
WITH THAT, 'CAUSE IT'S, UH,
YOU CAN DO BETTER THAN
THE "ICE MAN."
Rigsby, what you got?WHEN DAVID SEUNG GOT OUT
OF PRISON, HE WENT TO WORK
FOR A JANITORIAL SERVICES
COMPANY BASED IN OAKLAND.
RIGSBY FOUND
WHERE DAVID WORKED.
LISBON KNOW HE DID THAT?GOT AN ADDRESS?
I'M WORKING ON IT.
IT'S JUST...
What about
Seung's girlfriend?
GIMME A HINT
ON THE COIN TRICK.
Occam's razor.WHAT RAZOR?
BYE.
LET'S GO PAY A VISIT
TO DAVID'S OLD BOSS.WHAT'S THE POINT?
HE WAS A BANGER.
SO HE HAD IT COMING?YES.
LET'S GO AND SEE HIS BOSS,
GET A SECOND OPINION.
AND WHO'S THIS "K.S.,"
BY THE WAY?HE'S A GANG LEADER, BAD GUY.
WHAT'D YOU DO
TO MAKE HIM MAD?I SHOT HIM.
[car door closes]
THAT'LL DO IT.
YEAH,
I SAW DAVID LAST NIGI WAS DROPPING OFF PAYROLL
WHEN HE WAS STARTING HIS SHIFT.DID DAVID EVER MENTION ANYTHING
ABOUT THE AVON PARK PLAYBOYS?
HIS P.O. GOT HIM THE INTERVIEW.
I KNEW ABOUT HIS PAST.
WHY'D YOU HIRE HIM?I DON'T MIND HIRING EX-CONS.
THEY JUST NEED A SECOND CHANCE.
WHEN THEY GET ONE,
THEY APPRECIATE IT.
THEY'RE LOYAL.
IT KEEPS TURNOVER DOWN.
[man] HEY, YOU.FRANK. CAN I HELP YOU
WITH SOMETHING, MR. REED?
YEAH, DO YOUR JOB.
THE THIRD FLOOR MEN'S ROOM'S
A DISASTER.
WHOLE FLOOR'S
STARTING TO STINK.
MIDDLE MANAGEMENT.
EXCUSE ME?
YOU CATCH MORE FLIES
WITH HONEY--
IT'S A SOUND
BUSINESS PRINCIPLE,
OBVIOUSLY,
ONE YOU NEVER LEARNED.
HENCE, UH, MIDDLE MANAGEMENT.
[pops lips]
HAVE A NICE DAY.
HE'S GONE.
I STARTED THIS BUSINESS
THINKING IT'D BE NICE
NOT TO HAVE A BOSS.
TRUTH IS, I HAVE DOZENS.DO YOU KNOW WHAT THESE MEAN?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
NO IDEA AT ALL?
UH...
NO.
I-I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO TELL YOU GUYS.
NO NEED.THANKS FOR YOUR TIME.
NO PROBLEM. GOOD LUCK.
HEY, GUYS. I GOT A CALL
FROM DETECTIVE FLOREY
WITH OAKLAND HOMICIDE.
DID WE DECIDE TO TAKE OVER
THE DAVID SEUNG CASE
AND NOBODY BOTHERED
TO TELL ME?
BECAUSE SHE'S HEARING FROM
WITNESSES THAT YOU'VE TALKED TO.OH, UH, WE'RE JUST, UH.
PURSUING A LITTLE
INDEPENDENT INVESTIGATION.
WE DON'T DO THOSE.THAT'S MY I WAS CHECKING TO SEE IF DAVID
WAS STILL WITH THE PLAYBOYS.BALLISTICS CONNECTED
THE GUN USED TO KILL
HIM
WITH ANOTHER GANG SHOOTING
A YEAR AGO.
IT WAS THE PLAYBOYS.
GREAT.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GO SEE
THIS K.S. CHARACTER, HUH?
OR NOT.
SO I TOLD THE PROFESSOR
THAT THE EVIDENTIARY ISSUES
WERE SECONDARY
TO THE PROCEDURAL QUESTION,
AND SHE LOOKED AT ME
AND SAID,
"HEY, YOUR HAIR'S ON FIRE."
HELLO?
SORRY. I HEARD THAT.
HEARING ISN'T THE SAME
AS LISTENING.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
KIMBALL, YOU'RE TALKING EVEN
LESS THAN YOU NORMALLY DO.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
NOTHING.
WHICH MEANS SOMETHING,
BUT YOU JUST DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
WELL...
WE DON'T HAVE TO TALK.
THANKS.
[loud crash]ON THE FLOOR!
ON THE FLOOR!
HEY, HEY, HEY! TAKE IT EASY!SHUT IT!
HEY! GET DOWN! FACE DOWN![Elise] OH!
[Cho] HEY, YOU STAY AWAY
FROM HER!STAY OUT OF PLAYBOY BUSINESS!
[Elise grunting]
[siren wails,
indistinct police radio chatter]
SHE'S GOT SOME PRETTY BAD
BRUISING AND LACERATIONS,
BUT SHE'LL BE OKAY.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
JUST HANG IN THERE.
IT HURTS TO TALK.
ARE YOU OKAY?YEAH.
ARE YOU COMING WITH ME?
[whispers] I HAVE SOME THINGS
TO TAKE CARE OF FIRST, OKAY?
AND THEN
I'LL COME SEE YOU.
WE'RE TAKING OVER THIS CASE.
WE'LL LIAISE
WITH THE OAKLAND P.D.,
BUT WE'RE IN CHARGE. I'LL LOOK
INTO SUSPECTS WITH THE PLAYBOYS.
RIGSBY AND VAN PELT WILL GO
AND TALK TO THE PEOPLE
AT SEUNG'S WORK.
HE WAS SHOT TWO BLOCKS
AWAY FROM WORK.
MAYBE SOMEBODY SAW SOMETHING.
CHO?
WHERE WE GOING?
WHY DID YOU SHOOT K.S.?
I MEAN, IT'S A GANG.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME KIND OF RULES
AGAINST THAT SORT OF THING.
K.S. WANTED TO DO
A HOME INVASION.
YOU GO IN, HOLD THE FAMILY
HOSTAGE AND TAKE ALL THEIR CASH.
I WOULDN'T DO IT.
K.S. WANTED ME ON THE JOB.
WE ARGUED.
HE PULLED HIS GUN.
I PULLED MINE FASTER,
TAGGED HIM IN THE SHOULDER.OUCH.
THAT'S WHEN I LEFT THE GANG.
GAVE MY GUN TO DAVID.
A COUPLE OF DAYS LATER
HE BOOSTED A CAR.
THEY PULLED HIM OVER,
FOUND THE GUN ON HIM.
WITH THE POSSESSION CHARGE,
HE GOT 15 YEARS.
AND YOU FELT RESPONSIBLE
BECAUSE IT WAS YOUR GUN.
NO, I THOUGHT HE WAS STUPID
TO HAVE IT ON HIM.
NEVER SHOULD HAVE DONE THAT.AND THEN YOU JOINED THE ARMY?
ENLISTED TWO WEEKS LATER.
I WANTED TO GET
AS FAR AWAY AS I COULD.
TOLD MYSELF
I'D NEVER GO BACK.OKAY.
HEY. HOW'S BUSINESS?
JON JON'S GONE. YOU WANT
TO TALK, YOU GO FIND HIM.
NOT LOOKING FOR JON JON.
WHERE'S K.S.?WHERE'S K.S.?
UH, YEAH, SIMPLE ENOUGH
QUESTION, I THOUGHT.
WH--WERE YOU SERIOUS?
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
WHERE CAN I FIND HIM?I DON'T TALK TO COPS.
I'M NOT A COP TONIGHT. NO BADGE.
NOW WHERE IS HE?
I'M NOT LEAVING UNTIL I GET
AN ANSWER FROM YOU.
[grunts] AAH! [mutters]NOW I'M GONNA ASK YOU
ONE MORE TIME WHERE K.S. IS.
YOU DON'T TELL ME,
I'M GONNA BREAK YOUR ARM.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?SCREW YOU, MAN.
LET'S JUST RECONSIDER--SHUT UP! WHERE'S KI CAN DO THIS ALL DAY.
WHERE'S K.S.?!AAH! OKAY. OKAY, MAN. YOU'RE
GONNA BREAK MY ARM. ALL RIGHT.
[Lisbon speaks indistinctly]
HAVE EITHER OF YOU HEARD
FROM JANE OR CHO?
I CAN'T GET THEM ON THE PHONE,
AND THEY WON'T RETURN
MY MESSAGES.I DON'T KNOW. CHO HASN'T BEEN
TO THE HOSPITAL. I CHECKED.
DAMN.BOSS, I WENT OVER THE LIST OF
PEOPLE WORKING WITH DAVID SEUNG
THE NIGHT HE WAS KILLED.
FOUR OF THEM ARE WORKING
AT THE SAME JOB SITE TODAY--
A FINANCIAL FIRM CALLED
CEDAR CREEK EQUITIES.THAT'S THE PLACE WHERE JANE
AND CHO WENT TO, RIGHT?
YEAH.GO AND TALK
TO WHOEVER'S IN CHARGE.
SET UP INTERVIEWS WITH ANYONE
WHO WORKED WITH DAVID SEUNG.
AND IF YOU HEAR
FROM EITHER OF THEM, CALL ME.
WHAT DID HE CALL IT?OCCAM'S RAZOR.
WHAT IS IT?I HAVE TO LOOK IT UP.
IT'S SOME LOGIC THING.
BASICALLY IT SAYS
YOU SHOULD AVOID COMPLEXITY
WHEN SOLVING PROBLEMS.WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO
WITH FLIPPING HEADS 20 TIMES?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
HI. I'M AGENT VAN PELT.
THIS IS AGENT RIGSBY.
WE'RE FROM CBI.WHAT, DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
NO. BUT WE NEED TO SPEAK
WITH THE DIRECTOR OF OPERATIONS,
ADAM REED.
IS HE IN?NOT RIGHT NOW. UM, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO LEAVE A MESSAGE?
WE NEED TO TALK TO HIM
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
IS HE IN THE BUILDING?SURE. UM, BUT HE COULD
BE ANYWHERE,
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHEN HE'LL BE BACK.
THEN MAYBE YOU COULD CALL HIM
AND ASK HIM TO COME BACK?
RIGHT.
I GUESS I COULD DO THAT.
BAD COLD?HMM? [sniffles]
OH, IT'S ALLERGIES.
I, YOU KNOW,
THEY DRIVE ME CRAZY.
THAT'S K.S.'s HOUSE?
I'M GOING IN.
YOU STAY HERE. DON'T MOVE.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
[car door closes]
[sighs]
[horn honks in distance]
WE'RE LOOKING INTO THE MURDER
OF ONE OF YOUR EMPLOYEES,
DAVID SEUNG.YEAH. THAT WAS SHOCKING.
I SAW HIM AROUND THE OFFICE
OCCASIONALLY,
AND WE DIDN'T HAVE
ANY REAL INTERACTION.
I DON'T, UH, HANG OUT
IN THE MEN'S ROOM
CHECKING OUT
THE PAPER PRODUCTS, SO...
[chair hums]
[birds chirping]
YOU EVER SEE ANY ARGUMENTS
BETWEEN SEUNG AND COWORKERS?
NOT WITH STAFF.CLEANING CREW? I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK THEM.AND WHERE
COULD WE FIND THEM?
DOWNSTAIRS.
BUT, UH, MY GIRL CRYSTAL CAN
HELP YOU OUT WITH THAT ONE.
CRYSTAL!
YES, MR. REED?
YEAH, COULD YOU PLEASE TAKE
THESE AGENTS DOWNSTAIRS
AND LET 'EM TALK
TO ALL THE JANITORS?
[sniffles] SURE.AND ON YOUR WAY BACK UP,
COULD YOU PLEASE GET ME
A DECENT CUP OF COFFEE?YES, SIR.
THANK YOU.THANKS FOR YOUR TIME.
YOU BET.THANKS.
[gunfire]
[man] WHAT ARE YOU DOING?[man] HEY,
YOU GONNA SHOOT THAT?
NOBODY MOVE.
HANDS WHERE I CAN SEE THEM.
CHO.
K.S.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, MAN?
WE NEED TO TALK.GOT NOTHING TO SAY TO YOU.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU.
IN THERE. MOVE.
MOVE.
[book thuds]
GO ON.
I'LL SHOOT ANYONE
WHO COMES THROUGH THAT DOOR.
[closes door]WHAT IS THIS?
DID YOU KILL DAVID SEUNG?WHO?
[grunts]AAH!
[laughs]
GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO, BRO.
HAVEN'T CHANGED MUCH.
[grunts]
SOMEONE CAME TO MY HOUSE,
HURT MY GIRLFRIEND,
TOLD ME TO STAY OUT
OF PLAYBOY BUSINESS.THAT'S GOOD ADVICE.
YOU STILL MAD I SHOT YOU,
HUH?
NOT MAD.
DETERMINED.
I'LL SHOOT YOU AGAIN
IF YOU WANJUST KEEP TALKING WITHOUT
TELLING ME WHAT I WANT TO KNOW.YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO SHOOT ME.
TRY ME.
YOU'RE A COP.
YOU'LL DO WHAT THE MAN SAYS.
I'LL DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I DIDN'T PUT THE BEAT DOWN
ON YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
I DIDN'T KILL DAVID. OKAY?
DAVID CAME TO ME
A MONTH AGO,
WANTED TO BUY SOME COKE,
5 LARGE.
I HOOKED HIM UP.
THAT'S ALL I DID WITH HIM.
WHAT WERE YOU ARGUING ABOUT?THAT MUCH WEIGHT
WASN'T JUST FOR HIM.
I FIGURED HE WAS SELLING.YOU TOLD HIM TO CUT YOU IN.
YEAH.
BUT HE WASN'T DOWN FOR THAT,
SAID IT WAS A ONETIME THING
AND NO MORE.
YOU'RE LYING.
I'M TAKING YOU IN.
GET UP.
NOT GOING
TO A GOOD PLACE, CHO.
SHUT UP. GET THE DOOR.
MOVE.
HI.
YOU MUST BE K.S.
LET HIM GO.PUT YOUR GUN DOWN,
AND I'LL LET HIM GO.
NO WAY. YOU.
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, CHO?
IT'S ON YOU.
WELL, LET'S JUST TAKE A BREATH,
THINK ABOUT WHAT WE WANT.
YOU DON'T REALLY WANT
TO SHOOT ME.NO?
NO.
MY FRIEND AND I ARE COPS.
NO MATTER HOW CRAZY AND TOUGH
YOU ARE,
EVERYONE KNOWS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU KILL A COP.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY, YOU SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE IN PRISON.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY.
CHO.
YOU DON'T WANT TO SHOOT K.S.
YOU DO, YOU'LL NEVER FIND OUT
IF HE KILLED DAVID.
YOU'LL DESTROY YOUR CAREER
AT CBI.
SO LET'S JUST EMBRACE
THIS MOMENT
AND THINK...
ABOUT WHAT WE WANT...
AND JUST RELAX.
JUST...
LOOSEN UP AND RELAX.
[exhales deeply]
OH, YEAH. THAT FEELS
SO MUCH BETTER.
GET OUT.
NOW.
THANK YOU.
UH, ACTUALLY, I--
WHOA.
IT'S OKAY. JUST...
DON'T SHOOT.
JUST A PLASTIC BAG.
NOTHING TO IT.
THESE NUMBERS--
THEY MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
YOU ARE ONE STRANGE FREAK,
MAN.
OKAY. WELL,
I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO.
[bag rustles]
[door creaks]
WE SHOULD ARREST K.S.
AND BRING HIM THERE'S PLENTY
TO HOLD HIM ON.AH, HE'D COME IN
SURROUNDED BY LAWYERS.
IT'S NOT HIS FIRST TIME
IN AN INTERROGATION ROOM.
BESIDES,
I THINK HE'S CLEAN FOR THIS.CLEAN? HOW?
WELL, HE TOLD YOU THAT
HE SOLD THE DRUGS TO DAVID.
WH-WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
WHY WOULD HE KILL HIM?
WHAT'S THE MOTIVE?HEY. WOW, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
LIGHTER THAN AIR.MMM.
WHY'D YOU CALL HIM?OH, UM,
YOU'RE AN UNRELIABLE PARTNER.
I NEARLY GOT SHOT.
LOOK, IF DAVID WAS SELLING,
HE WAS USING. IF HE WAS USING,
HE COULD HAVE SCREWED UP
WITH K.S. A THOUSAND WAYS.SEUNG WASN'T USING.
HIS TOX SCREEN CAME BACK CLEAN.
JUST GOT THE REPORT. NO DRUGS.
SEE?WELL, THEN K.S. KILLED HIM
FOR ANOTHER REASON.
TOO COMPLICATED.
OCCAM'S RAZOR SAYS
THE SIMPLEST SOLUTION
TO A PROBLEM
IS USUALLY THE CORRECT ONE.
RIGHT?RIGHT.
RIGHT.
SO IF I FLIP A COIN,
AND I GET HEADS
20 TIMES IN A ROW,
YES, I COULD HAVE
RIGGED THE COIN.
BUT IF THE SIMPLE ANSWER
IS THE RIGHT ONE...
TWO COINS.
A 2-HEADED VERSION
TO FLIP...
AND A REAL COIN TO SHOW YOU,
MY FRIEND.[sets quarter on table]
I KNEW IT.WHAT'S THAT GOT TO DO
WITH DAVID?
DAVID BOUGHT
$5,000 WORTH OF COCAINE.
HE DIDN'T SELL AND HE WASN'T
USING. THINK SIMPLE.
WHO GOT THE DRUGS?
[sniffles]
[toilet flushes]
[sniffs]
[clears throat]
HI, CRYSTAL.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
[sniffles]
WE DON'T REALLY CARE
ABOUT THE DRUGS.
CRYSTAL, THIS IS
A HOMICIDE INVESTIGATION.
GIVE US A NAME.
WAS IT DAVID SEUNG?
YES.
YES, IT WAS DAVID SEUNG.
HE GAVE ME THE DRUGS.
NO. NO, YOU JUMPED AT THAT
A LITTLE TOO EAGERLY.
IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA  TO LIE TO US, CRYSTAL.
I CAN'T TELL.
HE'LL HURT ME.
OKAY.
HAS HE HURT YOU BEFORE NOW?
HOW?
[sighs]
UM... [sucks lip]
HE LIKES TO GET HIGH
AND BEAT ME
AND THEN HAVE SEX.
CRYSTAL,
THAT'S SEXUAL ASSAULT.
HE SOMEBODY YOU WORK WITH?
CRYSTAL, IF YOU TELL US HIS
NAME, HE WON'T HURT YOU AGAIN.
ADAM REED.
OKAY.AND DID ADAM GET THE DRUGS
FROM DAVID SEUNG?
YEAH. YES.
HOW?
ADAM CAUGHT DAVID
STEALING A LAPTOP,
AND HE KNEW THAT DAVID HAD
GANG CONNECTIONS,
SO HE FIGURED HE WOULD KNOW
PEOPLE WHO HAD ACCESS
TO GOOD COKE.
ADAM TOLD DAVID
HE WOULD TURN HIM IN
UNLESS HE GOT US THE DRUGS.
ADAM REED BLACKMAILED DAVID
INTO GIVING HIM THE DRUGS?
YES.
THANK YOU, CRYSTAL.
THAT WAS LOVELY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THESE MEAN?
UH...
I--WHERE DID--
HOW'D YOU GET THOSE?
[Adam] ONE FOR ME.
ONE FOR YOU.[woman laughs]
TWO FOR ME...[door opens]
OH.
[Cho] LADY, IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO GO TO JAIL, LEAVE NOW.
WHAT'S GOING ON, FELLAS?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS? 'CAUSE
FIRST OF ALL, THAT'S NOT MINE.
SHE BROUGHT THAT IN HERE.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.LET ME SEE YOUR HANDS.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
[handcuffs click]
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT.
SIT DOWN.
OH, YOU'RE A TRUE
RENAISSANCE MAN, AREN'T YOU?
BUSINESSMAN, DRUG DEALER,
BLACKMAILER, SEX ABUSER.
YOU TALKIN' TO CRYSTAL?
HUH? THE CRAZY COKEHEAD?
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
A WORD SHE SAYS.
OW!DON'T MESS WITH US.
OKAY.
THEN THERE'S THE SHOOTING
OF DAVID SEUNG.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THAT.WE THINK YOU DID.
YOU KNOW WHAT THESE ARE?
'CAUSE I DO.
THESE ARE PASSWORDS
TO FINANCIAL ACCOUNTS
OF SOME OF THE FIRM'S
WEALTHIEST CLIENTS.
DAVID SEUNG WAS STEALING THESE
WHEN HE WAS KILLED.
THE DRUG BUY--
THAT WAS JUST A WARM-UP.
THIS IS WHAT YOU REALLY
WANTED HIM TO DO, WASN'T IT?
YOU WANTED HIM TO STEAL
THESE ACCOUNT NUMBERS
SO THAT YOU COULD SELL THEM.
BUT SOMETHING WENT WRONGAND YOU SHOT HIM, DIDN'T YOU?YOU PEOPLE ARE INSANE.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THAT!
YOU DID.
THEN YOU BROKE INTO MY HOUSE
AND YOU BEAT ON MY GIRLFRIEND
AND THREW THE BLAME ON K.S.
AND THE PLAYBOYS, RIGHT?NO. I DIDN'T--OW!
[Cho] WHERE'S THE GUN, ADAM?[Adam] WHAT GUN?
I DON'T--
MAN, I WANT MY LAWYER
RIGHT NOW!
[Rigsby] HEY, CHO!
WHERE'S THE GUN, ADAM?WHAT GUN? AAH!
THE GUN YOU USED
TO KILL DAVID.
THAT'S CRAZY. MAN,
I WANT MY LAWYER RIGHT NOW.
AAH!HEY, CHO, YOU GOTTA
TAKE IT DOWN A NOTCH.
WE CAN TAKE HIM
BACK TO THE OFFICE, OKAY?
WE NEED HIM TO CONFESS. HE HAS
TO TELL US WHERE THE GUN IS.
IF WE DON'T HAVE THE GUN,
HE'S GONNA WALK.WE'LL GET THERE.
CHO, IT'LL BE FINE.NOW YOU GOT CUTS AND BRUISES
ON YOUR KNUCKLES.
YOU GET THOSE
WHEN YOU HIT SOMEBODY.
YOU WENT
TO MY GIRLFRIEND'S APARTMENT.
YOU PUNCHED HER IN THE FACE
UNTIL SHE BLED.
AND YOU KILLED
MY FRIEND DAVID. ADMIT IT.THAT'S FROM SOMETHING ELSE.
ADMIT IT!I DID! I-I BOUGHT DRUGS
FROM DAVID SEUNG.
I-I ADMIT THAT.
SO? THE REST OF THIS--I DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
LAST CHANCE.
YOU KILLED DAVID
AND YOU HID THE GUN. WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW.TOO BAD.
[grunts]
[Adam] AAH!
[Adam] WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WHERE ARE WE GONNA GO?
SHUT UP.[Rigsby] HEY! HEY!
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?COME ON.
[Rigsby] CHO! OPEN UP![Patrick] CHO! OPEN UP! CHO!
CHO, COME ON! CHO!
COME ON, MAN.
OPEN THE DOOR!
[Patrick] HELLO?![knock on door]
HEY! OPEN THE DOOR!CHO!
HEY!HEY! SOMEBODY!
HEY! HEY!OPEN UP.
COME ON. OPEN IT UP!
HI.THANK YOU.
THANK YOU. DO YOU KNOW
WHICH WAY THEY WENT?
THEY WENT THAT WAY.LEFT OR RIGHT?
LEFT. YEAH, THAT WAY.THANK YOU!
YOU SHOULD USE THIS
AS A LEARNING EXPERIENCE.[voice breaks] WHAT?
NO. PLEASE DON'T. PLEASE!
[thud]
CHO!
[gunshot]
OHH.
HEY! COME ON!
QUICK! KEY! YOU GOT A KEY?
QUICK.
GO.
OH, CRAP!
OH, HELL. CHO!
IS HE DEAD?
YES. HE WOULDN'T TALK.
OH, NO.
THIS IS NOT GOOD, CHO.
YOU'RE OUT OF CONTROL.HE MADE ME MAD.
AND YOU--YOU STAY
RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
RIGSBY,
PUT THE BODY IN THE CAR.OH.
PUT THE BODY IN THE CAR!RIGHT. YEAH. F-FINE.
I--LISTEN.
I WON'T TELL ANYBODY
ABOUT THIS.
BE QUIET! I'M THINKING!OH, WHAT'S TO THINK ABOUT?
HE DIDN'T CONFESS.
IF HE WAS GUILTY,
HE WOULD HAVE TALKED.I GUESS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, FRANK?
I DON'T--I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
REALLY?
WELL, THAT'S ODD,
'CAUSE... I THINK YOU LIED
ABOUT KNOWING THESE NUMBERS.
NO, YOU'RE--YOU'RE WRONG.ALL THOSE DAYS
CLEANING THE BATHROOM,
PICKING UP THE TRAIT MUST FEEL PRETTY GOOD GETTING
RICH OFF THEIR ACCOUNTS.I DIDN'T DO THAT.
WHAT'S WITH THE GLOVES,
FRANK?
THEY'RE WORK GLOVES.
YOU'RE NOT WORKING NOW.
TAKE THEM OFF. GO ON.
[Frank scoffs]IS THERE SOME REASON
YOU WON'T TAKE THEM OFF?
NO.MAYBE YOU GOT SOME CUTS
AND BRUISES ON THEM.
S-SLOW DOWN. THIS DOESN'T
HAVE TO END THE SAME WAY.
FRANK, JUST TELL US.
TELL US THE TRUTH.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU SHOT DAVID SEUNG.
NO, I DIDN'T!YOU SAID YOU WERE
DROPPING OFF THE PAYROLL
THE NIGHT THAT HE WAS KILLED.
YOU LIED TO US.
YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
I AM TRYING TO HELP YOU HERE.SHOW ME YOUR HANDS.
NO.SO JANE'S RIGHT.
IT WAS YOU.
NO!OH, FRANK.
FRANK, DON'T MAKE ME KILL YOU,
TOO. NOW YOU TELL ME THE TRUTH.
YOU TELL ME THE TRUTH,
AND I WON'T HURT YOU.
I-I-I-I'M NOT...YOU.
STOP! AAH! STOP! I CONFESS!
I KILLED DAVID!
DON'T LET HIM SHOOT ME!
PLEASE. PLEASE.
TELL THE TRUTH.HE'LL DENY IT LATER.
NO! NO! I-I-I-I BROKE INTO
YOUR GIRLFRIEND'S APARTMENT!
I CUFFED YOU!
I MADE YOU WATCH!
LOOK. SEE?
SEE MY HANDS?
WHERE'S THE GUN?
IN THE STORM DRAIN
OUT FRONT.
IT'S OKAY. I BELIEVE HIM.
I BELIEVE HIM.
RIGSBY.
WAIT.
YOU--YOU KILLED HIM.[Patrick] AH, NOPE.
CHO, HE'S CONFESSED.
YOU WON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HURT HIM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY.
OOH!
[siren wailing in distance]
WE FOUND THE GUN.
BALLISTICS ARE A MATCH.
YOU DIDN'T HIRE DAVID
TO GIVE HIM A SECOND CHANCE.
YOU HIRED HIM
TO STEAL FOR YOU.
HE WAS LIFTING
LAPTOPS AND DATA.
ALL YOU HAD TO DO WAS THREATEN
TO VIOLATE HIS PAROLE.
WHY KILL HIM?
HE WAS STEALING FOR YOU.
HE SAID HE WAS GONNA QUIT.
HE DIDN'T WANT ANY OF IT.
SAID HE JUST WANTED
TO LIVE HIS LIFE.
I THOUGHT HE WAS
GONNA TELL THE COPS.
THE OTHER GUNMAN THAT WAS WITH
YOU WHEN YOU BROKE IN ON ME--
WHO IS HE?
TONY WADE.
HE WORKS FOR ME.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
OKAY.
COME ON.
[door opens and closes]
MR. REED, I APOLOGIZE
FOR ACCUSING YOU
OF SEVERAL CRIMES
I KNEW YOU HAD NOT COMMITTED
AND FOR ASSAULTING YOU
REPEATEDLY.
THAT'S IT?
YES, THAT'S IT.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
VERY GOOD.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
THIS CASE WON'T LAST
30 SECONDS IN A COURT.
THE LAWSUITS, HOWEVER,
WILL LAST FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
COME ON, ADAM.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
AGENT CHO,
YOU'VE MADE
MY CLIENT A RICH MAN.[chuckles]
ONE MORE THING.
WHAT'S THAT?
WE HAVE TESTIMONY
FROM CRYSTAL HARGRAVE
THAT WILL LEAD TO MR. REED BEING
CHARGED WITH SEVERAL FELONIES.
THEY INCLUDE
NARCOTICS TRAFFICKING,
EXTORTION,
SEXUAL HARASSMENT--
NEVER BE ADMITTED.
FRUIT OF THE POISONOUS TREE.
NOT EVEN
FROM THE SAME FOREST.
OUR D.A. IS WILLING
TO TALK A DEAL WITH MR. REED
IN THE INTEREST
OF MENDING FENCES,
IF HE'S INTERESTED
IN MENDING FENCES WITH US.
[speaks indistinctly]
WE'LL SPEAK TO THE D.A.GOOD.
MRS. SEUNG.
MAY I COME IN?
THANK YOU.
WHEN I HEARD
DAVID HAD BEEN KILLED,
I ASSUMED IT WAS
BECAUSE OF THE MISTAKES HE MADE,
BECAUSE HE HADN'T CHANGED
HIS WAYS.
YES?
I WAS WRONG.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
DAVID HAD CHANGED.
DAVID CALLED ME...
TO ASK FOR MY HELP.
BUT I NEVER CALLED HIM BACK.
WHEN I LEARNED
HE'D BEEN KILLED,
I DIDN'T WANT TO ADMIT
THAT MAYBE HE'D
TURNED HIS LIFE AROUND,
BECAUSE THAT WOULD MEAN
ADMITTING THAT I LET HIM DOWN.
[speaking Korean]